/**
 * Created by jpollock on 9/21/2016.
 */
/**
 * Created by jonathanpollock on 9/20/16.
 */
var Questions = [{
        "question":"The main character in the 2000 movie Gladiator fights what animal in the arena?",
        "answer1":"Leopard",
        "answer2":"Lion",
        "answer3":"Jackal",
        "answer4":"Tiger",
        "correctAnswer":"Tiger"
    },
    {
        "question":"Typically, what level of school immediately precedes first grade?",
        "answer1":"Junior High",
        "answer2":"Kindergarten",
        "answer3":"Nursery School",
        "answer4":"Nursing School",
        "correctAnswer":"Kindergarten"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of the following beverages is carbonated water?",
        "answer1":"Coffee",
        "answer2":"Seltzer",
        "answer3":"Tea",
        "answer4":"Scotch",
        "correctAnswer":"Seltzer"
    },

    {
        "question":"In the 1950s TV series, The Little Rascals, who has a cowlick in his hair?",
        "answer1":"Buckwheat",
        "answer2":"Alfalfa",
        "answer3":"Froggy",
        "answer4":"Stymie",
        "correctAnswer":"Alfalfa"
    },
    {
        "question":"In military communications, What word is used to represent the letter C?",
        "answer1":"Caper",
        "answer2":"Charlie",
        "answer3":"Crook",
        "answer4":"Captain",
        "correctAnswer":"Charlie"
    },

    {
        "question":"What was the first name of the wife of President John Adams?",
        "answer1":"Abigail",
        "answer2":"Dolley",
        "answer3":"Maude",
        "answer4":"Alice",
        "correctAnswer":"Abigail"
    },
    {
        "question":"In what part of the human body would you find the temporal and zygomatic bones?",
        "answer1":"Chest",
        "answer2":"Hand",
        "answer3":"Leg",
        "answer4":"Skull",
        "correctAnswer":"Skull"
    },
    {
        "question":"What color is the leftmost in the NBC logo?",
        "answer1":"Red",
        "answer2":"Yellow",
        "answer3":"Green",
        "answer4":"Purple",
        "correctAnswer":"Purple"
    },
    {
        "question":"Melanoma is a type of cancer primarily affecting what part of the body?",
        "answer1":"Brain",
        "answer2":"Liver",
        "answer3":"Skin",
        "answer4":"Lungs",
        "correctAnswer":"Skin"
    },
    {
        "question":"In the 1996 animated movie The Hunchback of Notre Dame, who provides the speaking voice of Esmeralda?",
        "answer1":"Demi Moore",
        "answer2":"Rosie Perez",
        "answer3":"Kathleen Turner",
        "answer4":"Michelle Pfeiffer",
        "correctAnswer":"Demi Moore",
    },
    {
        "question":"According to superstition, to help sell your house you should bury a statue of which saint?",
        "answer1":"Saint Joseph",
        "answer2":"Saint Anthony",
        "answer3":"Saint Luke",
        "answer4":"Saint Paul",
        "correctAnswer":"Saint Joseph"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Greek mythology, what is the relationship between Oedipus and Antigone?",
        "answer1": "Husband and Wife",
        "answer2": "Mentor and Student",
        "answer3": "Father and Daughter",
        "answer4": "Mother and Son",
        "correctAnswer": "Father and Daughter"
    },
    {
        "question":"In the name of the British automobile, what does MG stand for?",
        "answer1":"Morris Grages",
        "answer2":"Mechanics Guild",
        "answer3":"Manchester Gearworks",
        "answer4":"Middlesex Grange",
        "correctAnswer":"Manchester Gearworks"
    },
    {
        "question":"In the first episode of the 1970s TV show Happy Days, the drive-in was called what?",
        "answer1":"Al's",
        "answer2":"Arthur's",
        "answer3":"Lenny's",
        "answer4":"Marshall's",
        "correctAnswer":"Al's"
    },
    {
        "question":"What author of Principles of Psychology coined the term stream of consciousness?",
        "answer1":"William James",
        "answer2":"Carl Jung",
        "answer3":"Alfred Adler",
        "answer4":"Anna Freud",
        "correctAnswer":"Carl Jung"
    }
];
















